Here's the Animal Constructor Function along with
这是一个 Animal 构造函数
the Walk method defined directly on animals prototype.
以及一个在 Animal 的原型上直接定义的 Walk 方法
Along with that, we also have the Cat Constructor Function.
此外 还有一个 Cat 构造函数
But, one thing you might notice is that we're using
但是 你可能注意到的一点是
the Call method over here in the cat constructor,
我们在 Cat 构造函数中使用了 call 方法
and we're invoking that directly on the animal constructor.
并且直接在 Animal 构造函数中调用它
The reason for this, is that we want to call
原因是 我们想要在 Cat 实例或 Cat 对象上
the super constructor on the cat instance or in the cat objects.
调用超级构造函数
Otherwise, this.name will actually be undefined.
否则 this.name 将是 undefined
On top of that, we're using call instead of the new operator when we want to invoke
此外 当我们想要调用 Animal 构造函数时
the animal constructor because we don't want to
我们使用 call 而不是关键字 new
construct a whole new animal object although,
因为我们不想构造一个全新的 animal 对象
all we really care about is just the animal initialization logic
我们只关心 cat 实例或 cat 对象上的
on the cat instance or on the cat object.
animal 初始化逻辑
Again, all the call method does is just invoke animal and sets this to the cat instance.
call 方法的作用是调用 Animal 并将 this 设为 cat 实例
Great. You can hit, Return.
按下 Return 键
And now, let's have this cat inherit from animal.
现在有了这个继承自 Animal 的 Cat
One more thing we need to do is change the constructor.
我们还需要更改构造函数
Otherwise, all cat objects will actually have their constructor point to animal,
否则 所有 cat 对象的构造函数将设为 animal
but it should point to cat. So let's change that.
但是它应该设为 cat 我们修改下
So, I'm going to clear the console to give myself a little bit more space here.
清空控制台 留出更多的空间
At this point, let's add a method to
现在 我们向 cat 的原型添加一个方法
the cat's prototype so all cat objects can share it. Let's call it meow.
使所有 cat 对象都能共享该方法 称之为 Meow
Now, we can call a cat constructor with
现在使用关键字 new 调用 cat 构造函数
a new operator and instantiate a new cat object. Let's call it Bambi.
并初始化新的 cat 对象 称之为 Bambi
And now, let's make sure Bambi has all the properties and methods that we wanted.
确保 bambi 具有我们想要的所有属性和方法
We have meow, we also have walk that we inherited from the animal constructor,
有 Meow 还有继承自 animal 构造函数的 walk 方法
and, of course, when we call bambi.name,
当然 当我们调用 bambi.name 时
we got Bambi's name.
获得了 Bambi 的名字
So, to recap, to efficiently manage inheritance in JavaScript,
总结下 为了在 JavaScript 中有效地管理继承
a great way is to avoid mutating the prototype
一个很好的方式是避免完全更改原型
completely and using object.create allows us to do just that.
为此 我们可以使用 object.create